evolution-slimming.com 2019-08-31

# Privacy Policy - Evolution Slimming Weight Loss & Nutrition

## This privacy policy sets out how Evolution Slimming uses and protects any information that you give Evolution Slimming when you use this website.

### What information we collect

#### We may collect the following information:

  * First name, surname and title
  * Contact information such as telephone number & email address
  * Demographic information such as address, IP address & postcode

#### What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Placing, processing and dispatching your order(s)
  * Internal record keeping
  * Analyse demographic and geographical location data via Google Analytics using cookies.
  * Provide you with website sharing services and social network connectors
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products & special offers
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes
  * We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests
  * Serve you adverts & reminders for our own products via display advertising, social media networks and email

#### Email marketing services

From time to time, we may contact you regarding offers and updates on our products and services. These emails may be personalised to contain your name for promotional reasons.

You may follow the ' **Unsubscribe** ' link in the footer of marketing emails to unsubscribe from them directly.

**Integration of the Trusted Shops Trustbadge**

Following an order, the Trusted Shops Trustbadge is incorporated into this web page in order to display our Trusted Shops trustmark for buyers and the eventually collected reviews, as well as the Trusted Shops product offer.

In balancing the various interests, this serves to safeguard our legitimate prevailing interests in an optimised marketing of our offer. The Trustbadge and the services advertised are an offer of Trusted Shops GmbH, Subbelrather Str. 15C, 50823 Köln.

Whenever a Trustbadge is called up, the web server automatically stores a so-called server log file which contains, for example, your IP address, the date and time of retrieval, the data volume transferred and the requesting provider (access data), and documents the retrieval. This access data will not be evaluated and will be automatically overwritten seven days after your visit to the page.

Other personal information will only be transferred to Trusted Shops if you decide, after completing an order, to use Trusted Shops products or have already registered for their use. In this case, the contractual agreement between you and Trusted Shops applies.

### How you can move or block cookie use at any time

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website and prevent you from placing an order.

### Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

### AdRoll

Evolution Slimming works with [AdRoll retargeting](http://www.adroll.com/ "AdRoll.com"), who uses technology including web beacons and cookies to collect data about our website usage and to improve the effectiveness of our marketing. Data recorded through the use of this technology is aggregated and shared with us.

No personally identifiable information about you is collected or shared by AdRoll with Evolution Slimming. You can opt-out of AdRoll and their partners by visiting this [link](http://www.adroll.com/about/privacy "AdRoll Privacy").

As you browse Evolution Slimming websites, advertising cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are interested in.  Our display advertising partner, AdRoll, then enables us to present you with retargeting advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with Evolution Slimming websites. The techniques our partners employ do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address or telephone number.  You can visit [this page to opt out](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/ "Advertising Choices") of AdRoll and their partners' targeted advertising.

### Advertising Partners

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. While each of these advertising partners has their own Privacy Policy for their site, an updated and hyperlinked resource is maintained here: Our advertising partners include:

  * Google - [Google Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacy/ "Google Privacy Policy")
  * Facebook - [Facebook Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/policy.php "Facebook Privacy Policy")
  * AdRoll - [AdRoll Privacy Policy](http://www.adroll.com/about/privacy "AdRoll Privacy Policy")
  * Yahoo! - [Yahoo! Privacy Policy](http://www.yahoo.com/privacy/ "Yahoo! Privacy Policy")

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology in their respective advertisements and links that appear on Evolution Slimming websites and which are sent directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by our site's third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on the site. Evolution Slimming websites do not have access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

### Klarna

Klarna's payment options, we want to pass to Klarna certain of your personal information, as well as contact and order details, in order to make sure you pay for your payment options and tailor the payment options for you. General information on Klarna you can find [here](http://www.klarna.at/) . Your personal data is handled in accordance with applicable data protection law and in accordance with the information contained in Klarnas [privacy statement](https://cdn.klarna.com/1.0/shared/content/legal/terms/0/en_at/privacy) .

### Newsletter

As part of the registration process for our monthly e-newsletter, we collect personal information. We use that information for a couple of reasons: to tell you about stuff you’ve asked us to tell you about; to contact you if we need to obtain or provide additional information; to check our records are right and to check every now and then that you’re happy and satisfied. We don't rent or trade email lists with other organisations and businesses.

We use a third-party provider, MailChimp, to deliver our newsletter. We gather statistics around email opening and clicks using industry standard technologies to help us monitor and improve our e-newsletter. For more information, please see **[MailChimp’s privacy notice](https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/).**

You can unsubscribe to general mailings at any time of the day or night by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any of our emails or by notifying us via our **Contact Us.**

### Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

Controlling your personal information

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
  * If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at enquiries@evolution-slimming.com.

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998.  If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to:

Evolution Slimming   
Unit 61 Maple Leaf Business Park,   
Manston, Ramsgate,   
CT12 5GD

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

#### Contact information

Evolution Slimming   
Unit 61 Maple Leaf Business Park,   
Manston, Ramsgate,   
CT12 5GD

Email: enquiries@evolution-slimming.com

Telephone: 0800 043 0434

This privacy policy was updated on June 7th, 2018.
